 [
    {
      
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",
      "option1": "Standard notation",
      "option2":"Tab notation",
      "option3":"Morse code notation",
      "option4":"Graphics notation",
      "answer": 3
      
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most common time signature in classical music?",
      "option1": "3/4",
      "option2":"4/4",
      "option3":"5/4",
      "option4":"6/8",
      "answer": 2
        },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",
      "option1": "Violin",
      "option2":"Piano",
      "option3":"harp",
      "option4":"Theremin",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      
      "question": "What is the most common key in pop music?",
      "option1": "C Major",
      "option2":"A Major",
      "option3":"D Major",
      "option4":"G Major",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of chord?",
      "option1": "Major",
      "option2":"Minor",
      "option3":"Diminished",
      "option4":"Flat",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",
      "option1": "Jazz",
      "option2":"Blues",
      "option3":"Rock",
      "option4":"Applesauce",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",
      "option1": "Harmony",
      "option2":"CounterPoint",
      "option3":"Form",
      "option4":"Cooking",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",
      "option1": "Allegro",
      "option2":"Andante",
      "option3":"Adagio",
      "option4":"Moderato",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",
      "option1": "Sonata",
      "option2":"Concerto",
      "option3":"Symphony",
      "option4":"Spaghetti",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",
      "option1": "Sibelius",
      "option2":"Finale",
      "option3":"Musescore",
      "option4":"Microsoft Word",
      "answer": 4
        }
  ]